Guide to the Maurice Shapiro Environmental Health Collection, 1919-2001 UA.90.F65
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Research Files, 1919-2000; IV.
  - Sewage, 1933-1975; 10.
    - 2208- Financing, 1947 (Box 27, Folder 29)
    - 2300- Urban sewage treatment, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 30)
    - 2300.1- Sanitary engineers conference, 1955 (Box 27, Folder 31)
    - 2300.1- Sanitary engineers conference, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 32)
    - 2301- History and financing, 1951 (Box 27, Folder 33)
    - 2301.1- Sewerage in Tokyo, 1963 (Box 27, Folder 34)
    - 2302- Small sewage treatment plants, 1948-1963 (Box 27, Folder 35)
    - 2302.1- Community planning for small sewage treatment plants, 1957-1965 (Box 27, Folder 36)
    - 2303- Filtration, 1951-1963 (Box 27, Folder 37)
    - 2305- Trickling filters, 1951-1956 (Box 27, Folder 38)
    - 2306- Individual treatment plants, undated (Box 27, Folder 39)
    - 2307- Municipal sewage and industrial wastes- Collection and treatment, 1952-1960 (Box 27, Folder 40)
    - 2308- Activated sludge process, 1952-1954 (Box 27, Folder 41)
    - 2308- Activated sludge process, 1954-1963 (Box 27, Folder 42)
    - 2309- Drainage, 1955-1956 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - 2310- Sewage disposal program of the Allegheny County Sanitary Authority, 1953-1959 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - 2311- Spiraflo clarifiers, undated (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - 2312- Sewage disposal, 1952-1960 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - 2312.1- Household sewage disposal systems, 1949 (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - 2312.1- Household sewage disposal systems, 1950-1954 (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - 2313- Water supply, sewerage and sewage treatment for public buildings, 1958 (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - 2314- B.O.D.- Effect of temperature, 1954-1963 (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - 2315- Oxidation ponds, algae symbiosis, 1946-1954 (Box 28, Folder 9)
    - 2315- Oxidation ponds, algae symbiosis, 1954-1959 (Box 28, Folder 10)
    - 2315- Oxidation ponds, algae symbiosis, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 11)
    - 2315.1- Algal growth, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 12)
    - 2316- Legislation, 1954 (Box 28, Folder 13)
    - 2317- Cities of Pittsburgh and Cincinnati, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 14)
    - 2318- Statistical summary of sewage works, 1950-1959 (Box 28, Folder 15)
    - 2319- Sewage characteristics, 1955 (Box 28, Folder 16)
    - 2320- Biocatalysis, 1953 (Box 28, Folder 17)
    - 2321- Irrigation, sewage farming, 1933-1957 (Box 28, Folder 18)
    - 2322- Biology, bacteriology of sewage and sewage sludge, 1962-1970 (Box 28, Folder 19)
    - 2323- Chlorination of sewage, 1945-1954 (Box 28, Folder 20)
    - 2324- Detergents, 1953-1961 (Box 28, Folder 21)
    - 2325- Micro-straining test and operating results, 1954-1959 (Box 28, Folder 22)
    - 2401- Digestion, 1954-1968 (Box 28, Folder 23)
    - 2401- Digestion, 1969-1971 (Box 28, Folder 24)
    - 2404- Incineration, 1954-1955 (Box 28, Folder 25)
    - 2405- Sludge conditioning and disposal, 1963 (Box 28, Folder 26)
    - 2406- Experimental studies on the concentration of raw sludge, 1946-1952 (Box 28, Folder 27)
    - 2501- Municipal sewer ordinances, undated (Box 28, Folder 28)
    - 2502- Laboratory guide for sewage works operators, 1950 (Box 28, Folder 29)
    - 2503- Recirculation system for toilet waste, 1937-1952 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - 2504- Sewer pipe, 1950-1959 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - 2600- Industrial wastes, 1954-1971 (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - 2600- Industrial wastes, 1972-1975 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - 2600.1- Control, undated (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - 2601- Atmospheric contaminants, 1945-1959 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - 2602- Radioactive waste disposal, 1955-1961 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - 2602.1- National Bureau of Standards handbooks, 1938-1958 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - 2603- Soap manufacturing, undated (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - 2604- Citrus industry, 1947-1954 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - 2605- Metal recovery by ion exchange, 1959-1961 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - 2606- Mine wastes, 1951-1952 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - 2607- Fluid solid separation processes, 1959 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - 2608- Waste treatment facilities, 1952-1959 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - 2608.1- Canton, Ohio, 1966 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - 2609- Naphthelene in industrial wastes, 1952 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - 2610- Chlorination of industrial wastes, 1941-1960 (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - 2611- Industrial wastes utilization, 1952-1955 (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - 2612- Pulp and paper mills. Dairy waste management, 1962-1970 (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - 2613- Oil industry, 1953-1970 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - 2615- Phenols, 1952-1953 (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - 2616- Milk processing, undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - 2617- Meat industry, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - 2618- Paper waste treatment, 1958-1971 (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - 2619- Phosphates and detergents, 1970 (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Sewage manual, Cattaraugus County, 1963 (Box 29, Folder 10)
  - Waste, 1953-1999; 11.
    - Allegheny County Hazardous Waste Task Force, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 11)
    - Allegheny County Industrial and Hazardous Waste Management Plan, 1981 (Box 29, Folder 12)
    - Allegheny County Sanitary Authority financial statements, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 13)
    - Allegheny County Sanitary Authority Sludge Management Plan, Volume 1, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 14)
    - Allegheny County Sanitary Authority Sludge Management Plan, Volume 2, 1980 (Box 29, Folder 15)
    - American Chemical Society meeting, 1968 (Box 29, Folder 16)
    - Articles, 1984-1985 (Box 29, Folder 17)
    - Attack on Hazardous Waste: Challenges of the 80s, undated (Box 29, Folder 18)
    - Baird, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 19)
    - Bettis: Radioactive wastes, 1960 (Box 29, Folder 20)
    - A Case Study of Solids Disposal Practices, 1983 (Box 29, Folder 21)
    - Center for Hazardous Materials Research, 1988 (Box 29, Folder 22)
    - Cheswick, undated (Box 29, Folder 23)
    - A Citizen's Solid Waste Management Project: Mission 5000, 1972 (Box 29, Folder 24)
    - City of Pittsburgh Citizens Task Force on Refuse Disposal, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 25)
    - City of Pittsburgh Water Treatment Plant, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Consortium for Biological Waste Treatment Research and Technology, 1984 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Contract Documents for Constructing Intercepting Sewers, 1955 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - COWAMP/208, 1976 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - The Design, Construction and Installation of a Solids Waste Disposal System for the County of Allegheny, Pennsylvania, undated (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Detailed Specifications for Secondary Treatment Facilities, 1969 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Determining the Feasibility of Resource Recovery, undated (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - Diaprotect 90, undated (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - Duquesne Light Company Shippingport Atomic Power Station, 1957 (Box 29, Folder 34)
    - Estimating Composition and Quantities of Solid Waste Generation, undated (Box 29, Folder 35)
    - From Pollution to Prevention, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 36)
    - Giardia cysts in raw and treated sewage, 1987-1989 (Box 29, Folder 37)
    - Governor's Waste Minimization Award, 1987 (Box 29, Folder 38)
    - Grunderville Sanitary Landfill, 1972 (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Handbook on Hazardous Waste Management, 1982 (Box 30, Folder 2)
    - Hazardous Materials Advisory Committee, 1975-1978 (Box 30, Folder 3)
    - Hazardous waste materials, 1978-1985 (Box 30, Folder 4)
    - Hazmat, 1983 (Box 30, Folder 5)
    - History of Coraopolis Sanitary Authority, undated (Box 30, Folder 6)
    - History of the Water System, undated (Box 30, Folder 7)
    - Human Factors Engineering and Wastewater Reuse, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 8)
    - Kosmos Cement Company, 1990 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    - Management of solid wastes, 1980 (Box 30, Folder 10)
    - Manpower, 1975 (Box 30, Folder 11)
    - Market Study: Interim Progress Report for Recoverable Resources, undated (Box 30, Folder 12)
    - McCandless Township Sanitary Authority, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 13)
    - Medical waste, 1988-1992 (Box 30, Folder 14)
    - Mellon Institute at Bushy Run, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 15)
    - Neufeld, Ron, 1979 (Box 30, Folder 16)
    - Newsletters, 1980-1981 (Box 30, Folder 17)
    - Nuclear Data, 1960 (Box 30, Folder 18)
    - Nuclear Measurements Corporation, undated (Box 30, Folder 19)
    - Nuclear Ohio, 1960-1961 (Box 30, Folder 20)
    - Nuclear waste, 1978-1985 (Box 30, Folder 21)
    - Packard, 1959 (Box 30, Folder 22)
    - Papers, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 23)
    - Pathological and Infectious Waste Disposal, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 24)
    - Pennsylvania Hazardous Waste Facilities Plan, 1986 (Box 30, Folder 25)
    - Pittsburgh Sanitary Engineering Conference, 1961 (Box 30, Folder 26)
    - Pittsburgh Sanitary Engineering Conference, 1970 (Box 30, Folder 27)
    - Plumbing the Future, 1999 (Box 30, Folder 28)
    - Pre-Operational Radiation Survey of the Shippingport Atomic Power Station Site and Surrounding Area, 1958 (Box 30, Folder 29)
    - Process Design Manual for Phosphorus Removal, 1971 (Box 30, Folder 30)
    - Process Design Manual for Phosphorus Removal, 1976 (Box 30, Folder 31)
    - Project Summaries, 1981 (Box 30, Folder 32)
    - Public Participation Program for Hazardous Waste Management in Pennsylvania, 1984 (Box 30, Folder 33)
    - Publications, undated (Box 30, Folder 34)
    - Quarterly Progress Report: Characterization of Substances in Products, Effluents and Wastes from Synthetic Fuel Development Processes, 1977 (Box 30, Folder 35)
    - Radioactive Waste Disposal in the Upper Ohio River Basin, 1962 (Box 31, Folder 1)
    - Radiation Counter Laboratories, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    - Radiation Instrument Development Laboratory, undated (Box 31, Folder 3)
    - Recommended Organization for Proposed Department of Solid Waste Management, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 4)
    - Removal of Color from TNT Waste, 1955 (Box 31, Folder 5)
    - Report: Committee of Refuse Collection and Disposal of the American Society of Civil Engineers, 1953 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    - Report: Proposed Collection and Treatment, 1948-1958 (Box 31, Folder 7)
    - Research proposal, 1967-1969 (Box 31, Folder 8)
    - Sanitary Engineering, 1954-1955 (Box 31, Folder 9)
    - Sewage position, undated (Box 31, Folder 10)
    - Solid waste, 1970 (Box 31, Folder 11)
    - Solid Waste Advisory Committee, 1970-1991 (Box 31, Folder 12)
    - Solid waste disposal, 1962-1970 (Box 31, Folder 13)
    - Solid waste disposal, 1971-1976 (Box 31, Folder 14)
    - Solid waste management recommendations, 1970-1971 (Box 31, Folder 15)
    - Solid Waste Research Committee, 1971-1991 (Box 31, Folder 16)
    - Surgeon General's Conference on Solid Waste Management, 1967 (Box 31, Folder 17)
    - A System for Prevention, Assessment, and Control of Exposures and Health Effects from Hazardous Sites, 1984 (Box 31, Folder 18)
    - Technical Measurement Corporation, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 19)
    - Travelab, 1960 (Box 31, Folder 20)
    - Urban Redevelopment Authority of Pittsburgh, 1981 (Box 31, Folder 21)
    - Waste stabilization ponds, undated (Box 31, Folder 22)
    - Waste Technologies Industries Hazardous Waste Incinerator Located in East Liverpool, Ohio, 1991 (Box 31, Folder 23)
    - Water and Sewer Systems Evaluation, Pittsburgh, 1983 (Box 31, Folder 24)
    - Westinghouse at Blairsville, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 25)
    - Westinghouse at Walty Mills, 1959 (Box 31, Folder 26)
    - World Health Organization, 1968-1969 (Box 31, Folder 27)
  - Water, 1930-2000; 12.
    - 1200- Water supplies, 1953-1955 (Box 31, Folder 28)
    - 1201- Cost, 1950-1967 (Box 31, Folder 29)
    - 1202- Housing, 1950 (Box 31, Folder 30)
    - 1203- Storage, 1957-1965 (Box 31, Folder 31)
    - 1204- Ground water supplies, 1936-1969 (Box 31, Folder 32)
    - 1205- Surface water supplies, 1950-1961 (Box 31, Folder 33)
    - 1205.1- Stream flow analysis, 1964 (Box 31, Folder 34)
    - 1206- Wells and cisterns, 1948-1957 (Box 31, Folder 35)
    - 1207- Laboratory control of water supplies, 1947-1960 (Box 31, Folder 36)
    - 1208- Individual water supplies, 1947-1950 (Box 31, Folder 37)
    - 1209- City of Pittsburgh, 1951-1961 (Box 31, Folder 38)
    - 1210- Concrete structures for farm water supply and sewage disposal, 1948-1959 (Box 31, Folder 39)
    - 1214- Instrumentation, 1947-1962 (Box 31, Folder 40)
    - 1215- Industrial water supplies, 1950-1963 (Box 31, Folder 41)
    - 1217- Drinking water standards, 1946-1959 (Box 31, Folder 42)
    - 1218- Ohio River, 1951-1964 (Box 32, Folder 1)
    - 1221- Water purification, 1955-1972 (Box 32, Folder 2)
    - 1222- Domestic consumer, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 3)
    - 1224- Water importation, 1972 (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - 1300- Water treatment, 1953-1958 (Box 32, Folder 5)
    - 1301- Design and operation, 1950-1970 (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - 1301.1- Equipment, 1962-1971 (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - 1302- Clarifiers, 1968 (Box 32, Folder 8)
    - 1303- Coagulation and filtration, 1951-1969 (Box 32, Folder 9)
    - 1305- Chemical (other than chlorination), 1950-1961 (Box 32, Folder 10)
    - 1305.1- Ozone, 1956 (Box 32, Folder 11)
    - 1305.3- Iodofors, 1952-1955 (Box 32, Folder 12)
    - 1306- Fluoridation, 1947-1955 (Box 32, Folder 13)
    - 1306- Fluoridation, 1955-1978 (Box 32, Folder 14)
    - 1307- Flocculation, 1950-1969 (Box 32, Folder 15)
    - 1308- Ion exchange, 1950-1966 (Box 32, Folder 16)
    - 1309- Removal of hardness, tubidity, color or algae, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 17)
    - 1310- Studies on radioisotopes, 1951 (Box 32, Folder 18)
    - 1311- Individual treatment plants, 1951-1965 (Box 32, Folder 19)
    - 1313- Natural purification processes (survival rates of organisms), 1951-1953 (Box 32, Folder 20)
    - 1314- Water softening (Permutit), 1951-1953 (Box 32, Folder 21)
    - 1315- Deaeration (Permutit), 1949-1952 (Box 32, Folder 22)
    - 1316- Filter bed agitators, 1950-1959 (Box 32, Folder 23)
    - 1317- Membrane filter in sanitary bacteriology, 1952-1958 (Box 32, Folder 24)
    - 1318- Millipore filters, 1953-1959 (Box 32, Folder 25)
    - 1319- Rapid sand filters, 1953-1958 (Box 32, Folder 26)
    - 1320- The Accelator, 1949 (Box 32, Folder 27)
    - 1321- Water tests, 1950-1953 (Box 32, Folder 28)
    - 1322- Distillation, 1953-1963 (Box 32, Folder 29)
    - 1324- Domestic purification, undated (Box 32, Folder 30)
    - 1326- Microwaves, ultrasonics, 1952-1953 (Box 32, Folder 31)
    - 1327- Odor control, 1951-1969 (Box 32, Folder 32)
    - 1328- Desalinization, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 33)
    - 1328.1- Measurements of ocean temperature and salinity, 1961 (Box 32, Folder 34)
    - 1400- Water pollution, 1952-1954 (Box 32, Folder 35)
    - 1400- Water pollution, 1954-1970 (Box 32, Folder 36)
    - 1400.1- Thermal pollution, 1961-1970 (Box 32, Folder 37)
    - 1401- Water pollution control, 1949-1957 (Box 32, Folder 38)
    - 1401- Water pollution control, 1958-1966 (Box 32, Folder 39)
    - 1401- Water pollution control, 1970-1971 (Box 32, Folder 40)
    - 1401.1- Research, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 1)
    - 1401.2- Storm and sanitary pollution control, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 2)
    - 1402- Water pollution control guide to source material, 1955-1960 (Box 33, Folder 3)
    - 1403- Legislation, 1958-1964 (Box 33, Folder 4)
    - 1403.1- Specific litigation, 1971 (Box 33, Folder 5)
    - 1404- Pollution in Missouri River, 1953 (Box 33, Folder 6)
    - 1405- Analysis of Allegheny Reservoir, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 7)
    - 1405.1- Allegheny River Project, 1959 (Box 33, Folder 8)
    - 1406- Water pollution in the United States, 1951-1962 (Box 33, Folder 9)
    - 1407- Clean streams, 1950-1987 (Box 33, Folder 10)
    - 1408- Underground water pollution, 1952-1959 (Box 33, Folder 11)
    - 1409- Algae, 1952-1958 (Box 33, Folder 12)
    - 1411- Leaching of ash dumps, 1952 (Box 33, Folder 13)
    - 1412- Water pollution research, 1940-1955 (Box 33, Folder 14)
    - 1412- Water pollution research, 1959-1961 (Box 33, Folder 15)
    - 1413- Industrials wastes, effects on rivers, 1950-1962 (Box 33, Folder 16)
    - 1415- Ohio River Valley Water Sanitation Commission, 1954-1964 (Box 33, Folder 17)
    - 1415.1- Ohio Water Pollution Control Board, 1964 (Box 33, Folder 18)
    - 1416- Legislation, 1950-1987 (Box 33, Folder 19)
    - 1417- Organic pollution, 1953-1960 (Box 33, Folder 20)
    - 1418- Stream pollution indicators, 1949-1959 (Box 33, Folder 21)
    - 1418.1- Sedimentation basins, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 22)
    - 1419- Toxicity (to fish, etc.), 1952-1962 (Box 33, Folder 23)
    - 1420- Limnology, plankton, 1952-1960 (Box 33, Folder 24)
    - 1420- Limnology, plankton, 1961-1963 (Box 33, Folder 25)
    - 1422- Phosphate, 1965-1971 (Box 33, Folder 26)
    - 1423- Marine pollution, 1956-1971 (Box 33, Folder 27)
    - 1424- Oil spills, 1970 (Box 33, Folder 28)
    - 1501- Planning for water distribution, 1945-1967 (Box 33, Folder 29)
    - 1502- Plumbing code, 1949-1951 (Box 33, Folder 30)
    - 1504- Cross connection survey, 1960-1964 (Box 33, Folder 31)
    - 1505- Appurtenances, 1953-1955 (Box 33, Folder 32)
    - 1601- Swimming pools, 1930-1959 (Box 33, Folder 33)
    - 1601- Swimming pools, 1959-1968 (Box 33, Folder 34)
    - 1602- Athlete's foot, 1963-1964 (Box 33, Folder 35)
    - Accomplishments under the Water Pollution Control Program, 1963 (Box 33, Folder 36)
    - Accra Tema Metropolitan Area, 1966 (Box 33, Folder 37)
    - Allegheny County communities, 1981-1990 (Box 33, Folder 38)
    - Allegheny County Emergency Water Supply Study, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 39)
    - Allegheny River Reservoir, 1957 (Box 33, Folder 40)
    - American Public Health Association, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 41)
    - Analysis of Organic Pollutants in (Drinking) Water, 1979 (Box 33, Folder 42)
    - Applicability of Rotating Biological Contractor Technology to Economic Water Pollution Control, 1980 (Box 33, Folder 43)
    - Articles and pamphlets, 1976-1986 (Box 33, Folder 44)
    - Assessment of Environmental Effects from the January 2, 1988 Diesel Oil Spill into the Monongahela River, 1990 (Box 33, Folder 45)
    - Assessment of Environmental Effects from the January 2, 1988 Diesel Oil Spill into the Monongahela River, 1990 (Box 34, Folder 1)
    - Bathing water quality research materials, 1961-1964 (Box 34, Folder 2)
    - Bibliography, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 3)
    - Cadmium Loadings on the Pittsburgh Wastewater Treatment Plant, 1975-1976 (Box 34, Folder 4)
    - Center for Environmental Epidemiology, 1979-1980 (Box 34, Folder 5)
    - Clean Streams, 1967 (Box 34, Folder 6)
    - Coastal Ecology Research Station, 1973-1974 (Box 34, Folder 7)
    - Common salts, 1953 (Box 34, Folder 8)
    - A Community Water Supply Report, 1977 (Box 34, Folder 9)
    - Conference on the Application of Engineering Technology to the Problems of Appalachia: Water Resources, 1965 (Box 34, Folder 10)
    - Congressional Research Service Brief: Safe Drinking Water, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 11)
    - Contingency plan- Monongahela and Ohio Rivers, 1988 (Box 34, Folder 12)
    - Control of the Pollution of Water Basins by Carcinogenic Hydrocarbons, 1964 (Box 34, Folder 13)
    - Cooling Towers and Water Quality, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 14)
    - Disinfection of water, undated (Box 34, Folder 15)
    - Disputes over Water Quality Policy, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 16)
    - Drinking water, 1974-1979 (Box 34, Folder 17)
    - Drinking water, 1980-1984 (Box 34, Folder 18)
    - Drinking water, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 19)
    - Drinking water, 1995-2000 (Box 34, Folder 20)
    - Drinking water and health issues, 1968-1979 (Box 34, Folder 21)
    - Drinking water and health issues, 1979-1986 (Box 34, Folder 22)
    - Drinking water and health issues, 1986-1988 (Box 34, Folder 23)
    - Drinking Water Research Strategy, 1980-1981 (Box 34, Folder 24)
    - Drinking Water Research Strategy, 1980-1984 (Box 34, Folder 25)
    - Drinking Water Task Force, 1975 (Box 34, Folder 26-27)
    - Economics of water, 1963-1965 (Box 34, Folder 28)
    - The Effect of Water Supply and Sanitation Investments on Health Status, 1980 (Box 34, Folder 29)
    - Emergencies, 1978 (Box 34, Folder 30)
    - Epidemiologic Appraisal of Water Quality, 1970 (Box 34, Folder 31)
    - ESE Notes, 1985 (Box 34, Folder 32)
    - Executive Summary of the Water Quality Standards Program, undated (Box 34, Folder 33)
    - Expanded Activities in Water Chemistry, undated (Box 34, Folder 34)
    - Federal Water Pollution Control Program, 1963 (Box 34, Folder 35)
    - Fluoridation, 1975-1987 (Box 34, Folder 36)
    - Fundamentals of Groundwater Quality Protection, 1984 (Box 34, Folder 37)
    - General Systems Approach to Groundwater Problems, 1968 (Box 35, Folder 1)
    - Global Water, 1983 (Box 35, Folder 2)
    - The Governor's Conference on Water Pollution Control, 1969 (Box 35, Folder 3)
    - Groundwater Resources, 1984 (Box 35, Folder 4)
    - Handbook for Monitoring Industrial Waste Water, 1973 (Box 35, Folder 5)
    - Hearing on Drinking Water Quality, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 6)
    - Historic and June 1972 Flood Elevations, Greater Pittsburgh Region (Box 35, Folder 7)
    - Hydroelectric power, 1958 (Box 35, Folder 8)
    - Hydrology, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
    - Intensive Study of the Water at Critical Points on the Monongahela, Allegheny and Ohio Rivers in the Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Area, undated (Box 35, Folder 10)
    - Interim Guidance for Preparation and Review of Environmental Assessments for Municipal Wastewater Treatment Projects, 1972 (Box 35, Folder 11)
    - Interim Report on Cresol, 1956 (Box 35, Folder 12)
    - International Association on Water Pollution Research, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 13)
    - International Conference on Peace, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 14-15)
    - International Conference on the Water Environment: Algal Toxins and Health, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 16)
    - International Symposium on Health-Related Water Microbiology, 1990 (Box 35, Folder 17)
    - Investigation of the Effects of Sanitary Landfills in Coal Strip Mines on Ground Water Quality, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 18)
    - Investigation of Water Quality at Beck's Run, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 19)
    - Lake Erie, 1968-1970 (Box 35, Folder 20)
    - Maintaining Clean Water, 1979 (Box 35, Folder 21)
    - Major Research Problems in Water Quality, 1965 (Box 35, Folder 22)
    - Marine Science Consortium, 1975 (Box 35, Folder 23)
    - McKeesport Water Authority, 1984-1986 (Box 35, Folder 24)
    - Measuring the Cost of Industrial Waste Pollution Control, 1976 (Box 35, Folder 25)
    - Mine Drainage Abstracts, 1974 (Box 35, Folder 26)
    - National Conference on Environmental Engineering, 1980 (Box 35, Folder 27)
    - National Pollutant Discharge Elimination System, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 28)
    - Oakmont Water Treatment Plant Emergency Contingency Plan, undated (Box 35, Folder 29)
    - Ohio River pamphlets, undated (Box 35, Folder 30)
    - Pennsylvania Department of Health, Division of Sanitary Engineering, 1966 (Box 35, Folder 31)
    - Pennsylvania Water Resources, Coordinating Committee, 1967 (Box 35, Folder 32)
    - Pennsylvania's Water Emergency Response Manual, undated (Box 35, Folder 33)
    - Physiological Aspects of Water Quality, 1961 (Box 35, Folder 34)
    - Pittsburgh Sanitary Engineering Conference, 1963-1967 (Box 35, Folder 35)
    - Pittsburgh's riverfronts, 1976-1977 (Box 35, Folder 36)
    - Planning Information Network for Southwestern Pennsylvania, 1977 (Box 35, Folder 37-38)
    - Plans and Choices, 1978 (Box 35, Folder 39)
    - Pollution, undated (Box 35, Folder 40)
    - Procedures for Evaluating Performance of Wastewater Treatment Plants, undated (Box 35, Folder 41)
    - Process Design Manual for Upgrading Existing Wastewater Treatment Plants, 1971 (Box 35, Folder 42)
    - Public Drinking Water Advisory Committee, 1993 (Box 35, Folder 43)
    - Publications, 1982-1989 (Box 35, Folder 44)
    - Pure Water, 1964 (Box 35, Folder 45)
    - Report on Pollution of Slippery Rock Creek, 1965 (Box 36, Folder 1)